bike-parts-honda.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy # HONDA Motorcycles & ATVS Genuine Spare Parts Catalog

Bike-parts-honda.com is part of the [Microfiches.net](https://en.microfiches.net/) group which is edited by Coxa Ltd.

Coxa Ltd ("we" or "us") is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and you can trust us to do it carefully and sensibly.

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, manage, process, store and share the personal information you provide us through bike-parts-honda.com. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of applicable data protection laws and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679), the Data Controller is Coxa Ltd, whose registered address is Office 10, 10-12 Baches Street, London, England, N1 6DL.

 **PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**

You provide us your personal information by creating an account, placing an order, signing up to our newsletter, corresponding with us by e-mail, telephone or social media. It includes information you provide when you search for a product, report a problem with our website via customer service or other social media. The personal information you provide us may include but is not limited to your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information. **We will only request information which is required for the specific purpose**.

By submitting this data, you give your consent that we collect and process the data to provide you with the information, products and services that you requested from us. In such case, the legal basis for the processing is Article 6 (1) (a) GDPR. You have the right to withdraw this consent at any time. We may also use this data to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered between you and us. In such case the legal basis is Article 6 (1) (b) GDPR. We store your personal data only as long as we need it to provide the information, services or offers you requested or to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts.

We automatically receive the following information when you visit bike-parts-honda.com

\- Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, device types, operating system, time and date of consent and platform.

 \- Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), products you viewed, searched for or purchased, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse the website, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

 **WHY WE PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

 **We collect your personal information in order to provide you with the best user experience possible on bike-parts-honda.com  and also continually improve our services.** 

We use your personal information to:

\- Take and handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products & services.

\- Improve usability, effectiveness & functionality

\- Analyze performance & fix errors

\- Personalise your experience

\- Recommend services that might be of interest to you

\- Comply with legal obligations

\- Communicate with you by e-mail or phone

\- Detect & prevent fraud to protect you and us

We reserve the right to check these log files and data retroactively if there is reasonable suspicion of an illegal act due to concrete indications. As far as personal data is processed, we do so solely to protect our legitimate interest to control illegal acts particular in connection with our website. The legal basis for this is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR.

We may receive personal information about you from other sources if you use any of the other [Microfiches.net](https://en.microfiches.net/) group websites we operate or the other services we provide. We are working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers). We will notify you and ask for your consent when we receive personal information about you from them and the purposes for which we intend to use that information as well as the legal basis for such processing. You may withdraw your consent at any time and we will stop processing of your data for that purpose.

We use information held about you if you have provided your consent for the use of your data for marketing purposes, we will contact you by electronic means (e-mail) with information about goods and services like those which were the subject of such consent. The legal basis for this processing is Article 6 (1) (a) GDPR. You have the right to withdraw this consent at any time by contacting us at **data.privacy@microfiches.net**

Third parties, we are working closely with, may also use information held about you if you have provided your consent, to permit these selected third parties to use your data, to contact you by electronic means (e-mail). The legal basis for this data processing is Article 6 (1) (a) GDPR. You have the right to withdraw this consent at any time by contacting us at **data.privacy@microfiches.net**

 **COOKIES**

Bike-parts-honda.com uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and allows us to improve your experience. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies". Other cookies remain on your device until you delete them. These cookies allow us to recognize your browser at the next visit. As far as personal information is processed in this regard, we carry out such processing on basis of our legitimate interest to improve our website for users. We only process pseudonymised data in this regard upon your visit of our website. The legal basis for such processing is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. You can delete cookies on your device at any time and once they are deleted we cannot process any information contained in a cookie. You can further adjust your browser so that you are informed about the setting of cookies and only allow cookies on an individual basis, exclude accepting cookies for specific cases or in general, and activate the automatic deletion of cookies when you close your browser. The functionality of bike-parts-honda.com may be restricted when cookies are disabled.

 **GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

Bike-parts-honda.com uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze your use of our website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website will be transferred to a Google server in the United States. We use Google Analytics with the extension "anonymizeIp", so that the IP addresses transferred to Google are only processed in a shortened version in order to exclude that they are directly related to you. Google will use this data for the purposes of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for our website, and providing further services related to website and internet usage. Google may also transfer this data to third parties, provided that it is required by law or insofar as third parties process this data on behalf of Google. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You can prevent the installation also of the Google Analytics cookie by the settings of your browser software. We point out that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of our website. Furthermore, you can object to data collection and storage for Google Analytics for the future at any time via Google’s browser plug-in (<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>). For more information about Google Analytics go to (<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>).

As far as personal information is processed in this regard, we carry out such processing as part as of our legitimate interest for own marketing purposes. We safeguard your interests by anonymizing your IP address upon collection so that you are not identifiable. The legal basis for such processing is Article 6 (1) (f) GDPR. 

 **SECURITY**

Your security & privacy is essential to us this is why bike-parts-honda.com is secured by an SSL certificate (Secure Sockets Layer) which encrypts the information you input. You can see that a website is secured by an SSL certificate when https (Hyper Text Transfer Protocol Secure) appears in the URL and that there is a lock symbol in the browser bar.

All personal information you provide us is stored on our secure servers. Our security procedures mean that we may request proof of identity before we disclose information. It is important for you to protect your password against unauthorised access. Take care to logout when you have finished using a shared computer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is never completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website, any transmission is at your own risk.

 **SHARING YOUR INFORMATION**

We do not sell your personal information in any case! Bike-parts-honda.com shares your personal information only as described below and with the [Microfiches.net](https://en.microfiches.net/) group.

We may transfer your personal information to third-parties if legally required or if we instruct third parties to process your data under our authority, but this will be done following strict adherence to applicable laws and regulations. In this regard your data may also be processed by staff which might be operating outside the European Economic Area who work for us, our affiliates or for one of our suppliers. This includes staff engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

 **RETENTION PERIOD**

We retain your personal information to enable your continued use of bike-parts-honda.com, for the period necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by applicable law such as for tax & accounting purposes. For example we keep your order history for you to be able to review all your information of past purchases. 

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

As a data subject, you have the right to assert the rights of the data subject towards us at any time. In particular, you have the right to:

\- Obtain information whether and if applicable to which extent we process personal data concerning you or not.

\- Access stored data concerning you, purpose(s) of the processing, categories of data, recipients to whom we disclose data, duration of the storage.

\- Request the rectification of your data without undue delay, as far as they are inaccurate or incomplete.

\- Request the deletion of your personal information from us without undue delay.

\- Withdraw your consent given to us concerning the processing of your data at any time.

\- Let the processing of your personal data be restricted.

\- Receive you’re personal data which you had provided to us in a structured, standard and machine-readable format, and to transmit these data to another controller.

You may assert your rights by contacting us at **data.privacy@microfiches.net**

 **PARTNER & THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal information to these websites.

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, regulatory or operational requirements. Please read our Privacy Policy frequently to acknowledge these changes.

 **CONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed by email to **data.privacy@microfiches.net**

This Privacy Policy takes effect on the 23rd of May 2018
